Hey, Pucchi… Did you know?
The average number of daily visitors
at the Louvre, Paris in the spring
is about 40,000.
Since its doors opened in 1793,
more than 40,000 people flock
to view the Mona Lisa
and the Venus de Milo every day.
The visitors do not leave
without seeing these two pieces.
Isn't that incredible?
Incredible?
Do you mean the number of guests?
That's not it.
Some of the world's
greatest painters and sculptors
are able to express their souls
in a form that can be seen by eyes.
It's as if they create Stands
that exist beyond time and place.
Wouldn't you agree?
It's an interesting thought.
Does that make Leonardo Da Vinci
and Alexandros of Antioch Stand Users?
Yes, but I'm also talking about you.
Your Pale Snake
is able to extract and store souls
by giving it form.
Will you betray me one day?
Why do you not attack me?
You know that
I would not survive in sunlight
and that I lay to rest
in the dark room during the day.
All you have to do is
finish me off while I sleep.
If you turn my Stand, The World,
into a disc and take it,
you yourself could become king.
So do it.
That has never even crossed my mind.
I like people who help me grow.
You are the king among kings.
I want to follow you
and see what kind of end you will reach.
I love you, in the same manner
as men love their god.
Sorry, that wasn't meant to insult you.
It's that I've never considered
that there was a man
who could calm my soul just by us talking.
I feared losing you.
You will become a noble priest.
Please, accept this.
It is a symbol of my apology.
I extracted it out of my body just now.
No matter where you are, I will always
be able to lend you my powers.
EPISODE 22: TIME FOR HEAVEN!
NEW MOON! NEW PRIEST!
Jo…
Jolyne!
Pale Snake.
Read Jolyne's whereabouts from that disc.
Respond to me.
What happened?
Is that you there?
Respond to me.
Can you not hear me?
Why is this transceiver here?
Who is on the other end?
Who?
Who the hell is it?
All right.
I understand.
The situation is that serious, huh?
I just left the medical wing.
Bastard!
It's Weather Forecast!
This rain…
Where is the disc?
This bastard!
They had Weather Forecast summon rain!
You won't escape me!
Damn this rain!
I can't see anything… where did they go?
And it's foggy.
Where is this sound of
hitting rocks coming from?
I think it's Morse Code?
Make the fog thicker…
They're after me.
Pale Snake's User is Father Pucchi!
He knows.
He knows who I am!
Weather Forecast knows!
Five hundred three.
Count the prime numbers.
Five hundred nine.
Five hundred twenty-one.
Nothing can divide prime numbers.
The reason why people lose…
Five hundred twenty-three.
Shame leads men to defeat.
Men die to compensate for their shame.
Five hundred forty-one.
Thoughts of shameful regret
such as "why did I do that earlier"
weakens men
and leads them to their defeat.
I didn't make an error by failing
to see the guards' transceiver.
No, this is a trial.
There are still ways to prevail.
Jolyne Cujoh doesn't know who I am yet.
Nothing has changed yet.
I haven't completely lost them, either.
True victors…
are those who can reign over
the circumstances given to them.
It looks like you survived.
Weather Forecast.
Where are Jolyne and the others?
Anastasia.
I'm really grateful
for everything you've done for me.
Thanks to you, I've been safe until now.
But why do you care so much about me?
Finding out who Pale Snake is
and getting my father's memory back
is my problem, and mine only.
Jolyne, how can you say that
when you fully know
how I feel towards you?
You've already given me so much.
I see a bright hope
I couldn't find anywhere,
inside or outside of the prison.
And that's why I'm here with you.
Hey, what's this?
Why is it latching onto me?
I'm not sure.
"I'm not sure" isn't an answer.
It's chewing on my hair!
It's eating dirt too.
So, is it actually a plant?
Does it need nutrients?
But it sleeps a lot too.
Jolyne, get down.
Something is coming.
There are two of them,
and they've already closed in on us.
F.F.!
Jolyne… I know who Pale Snake is.
It's Father Pucchi, Jolyne.
It was Father Pucchi all along.
I almost died.
If Weather Forecast hadn't come,
I wouldn't be alive right now.
F.F.!
I'm fine.
I only threw out my body.
What happened to you guys, Jolyne?
Let me heal your right eye.
What you said just now…
Yes. Father Pucchi
was trying to track down
the baby's location from D an' G's memory.
Now, we only need to corner him.
There's finally a way for us to win.
Weather Forecast came too.
Weather Forecast.
Jolyne…
Have you recovered from the injuries
you sustained at the factory?
Yes. I hope you've been okay.
What the hell is this?
What are those two doing?
They are embracing.
I know that much! F.F., separate them!
Separate them now!
I have to do it?
Yes, you!
Remember our terms?
That asshole's smell
is rubbing off on Jolyne!
Calm down, it's just a greeting!
See? They stopped.
Stop being dramatic.
We found out Pale Snake's identity.
We don't have time for this petty fight.
Hey, are you talking back to me?
What the hell are you thinking?
How dare you forget our promise.
You are nothing but plankton.
Jolyne, now that we know
who Pale Snake is,
we don't need this thing anymore.
There's no use for it.
Let's kill it.
Give me permission, Jolyne.
Wait a minute.
It's not your ally, Jolyne.
It's not even human.
It didn't exist in the first place.
This being is lower than animals.
It should have never been born.
We shouldn't keep unknown creatures
like this one alive.
So please, let me.
Now hold on.
You better watch it, Anastasia.
Are you talking about me?
Careful how you phrase things.
Don't touch me.
We don't have time for that, plankton.
Weather Forecast,
you know the situation, right?
Give me permission.
No. I cannot do that.
You are the one who will die.
F.F., who the hell did you bring?
Bastard…
Fuck, you got me.
This can't be.
This isn't… This can't be happening!
He's not Weather Forecast.
He's…
We were… being tricked.
Thank you, F.F., for taking me here
before the real Weather Forecast
caught up.
Five hundred forty-seven.
Five hundred fifty-seven.
No one can divide prime numbers.
It took such a long time.
I waited 22 years.
The pinnacle of heights
humans are able to achieve…
This is undoubtedly it.
We finally meet,
you who will help me get to heaven!
Though incomplete and inchoate,
the only thing left for me to do is to
trace the memory sealed by Jotaro Kujo.
The new moon rises tonight.
Dio.
No other night is better suited
to awaken you once again
so that you benefit my cause.
Thirty-six of the worst convicts' souls
were absorbed
and gave rise to this new life form.
That's what this green creature is.
That reminds me.
Before I begin…
I must send you to an absolute death
where you are forever forgotten.
Now stand, Jotaro's daughter.
Though I struck a fatal blow,
you managed to block
a split second faster than the others.
If you won't attack, then I will!
I didn't think
this was how I'd find out
who you were, Pale Snake.
I didn't think
I'd see you again like this.
I'm taking three things from you.
My father's memory,
the disc you took from F.F.,
and your life!
What is the meaning of these handcuffs?
You've never worn handcuffs before?
I had to wear them almost every day
ever since your ploy brought me here.
You think you caught me with these?
Do you know what handcuffs are for?
They aren't to keep someone
from running away.
They are used to make others submit!
You still don't seem to understand
what you are doing right now.
We are connected through these handcuffs.
Do you know what that means?
Let's see who is the one
that's being kept here.
I already turned your Stone Ocean
into one of my discs.
It's so close to falling out,
I can almost grab it.
Do you see it now?
So who is the one in a predicament here,
you or me?
Well, I really don't get
what you are on about…
That's all I know.
A few millimeters.
A few millimeters, and this fight is over.
If I can enter just a few millimeters
within my range of aerial attack,
my fist can land a blow.
Some swallows die from flying
directly into cliff walls.
It's because their parents
never taught them the safe diving range,
leading the swallows
to soar at a dangerous angle.
It's not that the birds' parents
aren't teaching their offspring.
The parents cannot teach it because
their own parents never taught them.
This family of birds tends to have
a short lifespan,
and they don't even realize why
they're prone to dying from accidents.
Jotaro had a short lifespan.
Stone Ocean is mine!
I used her own disc to block her sight…
How did she know where I was?
Did she use the cuff's vibrations
to guess?
No, it's her strong will!
Her strong will detected my attack!
When she first entered prison,
I thought she didn't even have
a Stand ability.
She seemed like a helpless little girl
crying over some asshole who used her.
This is bad.
Her Stone Ocean has an advantage
over my Pale Snake.
At this rate, I'm done for…
But more importantly,
the birthed creature will be destroyed!
What did you throw just now?
What did you do?
I'm asking you what you threw!
A disc is a physical manifestation
of one's soul.
It can be stored forever.
However,
what if the disc is inserted
into someone on the brink of death?
The disc would perish
along with that person's death.
That's Jotaro's memory disc
you've risked your life for.
You can have it back.
It's stabbed into Anastasia's dying body.
What will you do now?
Will you go get the disc?
Or will you continue
your handcuff death match?
It's risky to let go of Jotaro's disc,
but I've already memorized
the contents of the notebook.
All that is left is the execution.
What will you choose, Jolyne Cujoh?
How can you still be contemplating?
Your father is rotting away
along with Anastasia as he wastes away!
All that I'm after
is the birthed creature.
I won! As I thought, she chose her father.
Spiral staircase, rhinoceros beetle,
city of desolation, fig tart,
rhinoceros beetle, Via Dolorosa,
rhinoceros beetle,
singularity point, Giotto,
angels, hydrangea, rhinoceros beetle,
singularity point,
secret emperor.
You've shown your interest.
Are you willing to approach me?
Will this be the beginning of everything?
Now, I can depart
into your world with you!
Hallelujah, Dio!
Anastasia!
This can't be happening…
No… this can't…
This isn't true!
Somebody!
Isn't there anyone around here?
Somebody! A guard! I'm right here!
Please, I need a doctor!
- Hey!
- Diver…
- Diver… Drive.
- Please, somebody!
- Can you hear me?
- Please, call for help!
- F.F…
- Please!
- Help!
- Jolyne is mourning.
This is your fault, F.F.
Shit…
I'm cold.
Actually, I'm freezing.
Looks like my heart's
already stopped beating.
I guess her father's memory disc
is inside my body.
It will disappear, along with my life.
I tried to eject it,
but I'm fighting to stay awake.
Looks like you are crumbling away.
Come claim my everything.
You have to be the one to do it.
I'll leave my intellect for your use.
You can use up all the life
I have left in me too.
You can have my body.
So come inside my body
and remove the disc for Jolyne.
Only you can do it, plankton.
Answer me, F.F.
We made a deal!
You are supposed to follow all my orders.
You have to keep your word.
You have to stay alive.
You can mutate my body as you please.
Stop wasting time!
My… consciousness…
It's… going…
This can't be!
Anastasia!
No… Jolyne.
It's going to be all right.
It's not how it looks.
You've done it.
Anastasia…
got the disc back for you.
F.F., is that you?
Are you the one speaking?
One thing I feared the most
was losing the ability to even think
to say goodbye to my friends.
But…
in the final moment, I could do just that.
Jolyne,
please tell this to Anastasia
once he wakes up.
His body belongs to himself.
I used his life and intellect
to fill his wounds.
Hold on!
Why are you talking like this, F.F.?
Goodbye, Jolyne.
I can't be here any longer.
F.F. is disappearing.
What are you saying?
Stop talking like that!
Look at me, Jolyne.
This is my soul.
This is my intellect.
I lived a life.
I'll do anything to get your disc back
from the priest.
I'm talking about F.F.'s disc.
That will bring you back!
That must be a different F.F.
I don't think it would be me.
Because this is me.
This is me, saying goodbye.
I'm so glad I got to say
my farewells… Jolyne.
This is all right, Jolyne.
Everything is all right.
I'm glad you got your father's disc back.
F.F…
Respond, F.F.
I've lost you, F.F.
Where are you?
F.F.?
Answer me, F.F.
F.F.
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter